Oh! Oh! Oh!
I didn't know it was going to be like this.
This is so fun!
Oh my gosh!
We won it ourselves.
We can afford it.
Oh!
The winner, Ichikawa!
Ichikawa!
The winner, who may not even have a nice face, Ichikawa!
I may not be good-looking.
Face out, face out!
Now, so the final is between Yuzu and me, but before that, I'd like to have the championship game!
It seems like this one is faster, so we'd like to have a match to determine who is the winner of the argument. I'd like to see who is the winner of the debate. I'd like to see who has the best view of the argument. Yes, that's right.
Are you talking about who is the "argumentative viewpoint"?
I would like to decide who it is.
Hana and Moeka. I would like to hear their enthusiasm.
Let's start with Hana.
I definitely don't want to lose to such a chin-chick.
I see.
I definitely don't want to lose to someone who cries over a lie.
They're bees, aren't they?
They are bees. I think we can expect a lot from him.
But it's not downstream.
Downstream?Downstream?
I know you're mineMy pretty boy
My life
Girl
I'ma be your mine
Tell me now
It's up now, it's about you and it's about you and it's about you
It's up now, it's about you and me
So baby
My favorite fruit
I knew you two had a thing for guffaws.
You want to say something?
What did you want to say?
I don't know. It's a combination of "bilge" and "vomit".
I don't know.
I don't know. It's like we're both vomiting.
It's like we're laughing at each other or something, and people might notice.
I won't laugh so you won't notice.
I won't laugh.
I'd like you to be careful there.
I never laugh. I would like you to be careful there.
Please.
Now, please move five fine steps.
One, two, three, four, five.One, two, three, four, five.
Two, starting with one.
Yes, sir.
Let's do it.
All right, let's go!
Ah! Oh! Yay! Winner, Hana! Yeah!
Yeah!
Mike, you're sticking your mouth out again.
You should've noticed that on the way in. Um... flowers.
Yeah!
Yes!
Yes!Yes!
Pattern! Yeah! Mike, you were right about the pattern.
I noticed it on the way in, Mr. Hecok.
It was a good match.
Great.
Mr. Suzuki, Mr. Suzuki.
I'm a girl. I can't win a fight or anything.
And so, now it's time for the finals.
The final is between Aiara, Yuzu and Heiwa.
Well, first of all, Aira, what's your motivation?
I won't be beaten by this hero girl with horns growing out of her head!
That's right!
Ichikawa-san, go ahead.
Yes, sir! Even in heels, Yuzu can beat this mook by a comfortable margin!
Let's throw down the gauntlet.
We're in the finals, so we're already bouncing around.
Here we go.
More soon, then.
Wait, I'm really saying it, I'm getting yankee blood, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're bleeding Yankee blood.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
The wind's coming.
Here we go.
It's going around a little too far.A little too much going around.
It spins too much for five minutes with that sensibility.
I'm not spinning.
Wait a minute, yes, OK, you don't have to try for five minutes with the nail clippers, but wait a minute, I'm always with you.
Wait a minute.
Okay, okay.
Oh, no, no, no, stop.
Oh, no, no, no, no, stop.
Oh, I'm getting stung.
One, two, three, four, five.
You want me to bite my nails off?
Ready, go!
Oh, that's so cool. I don't care if it comes or goes.
That's what I'm talking about. This is the final. This is on a different level.
It's so cool!
He's so sharp.
You didn't stop.
Wow.
Isn't that Aiara?
It's Aiara, isn't it?
You hit it, didn't you?
We did, didn't we?
Yeah!
Yay.Yay!
I won!
The winner is Aiara!
Oh!
Two winners in a row for Aira? Yes! But first, we all agreed that Aira was the most sensitive and outspoken, right?
Yeah...
Who is the crass woman who is far from sensitive or sensible?
You mean someone who's not sensitive.
Okay, let me see it here, for God's sake.
Okay.
What, me?
Well, for starters, you want to meet someone normal, someone who isn't... What? Me?
That's okay.
Let's start with you.
You said it yourself.
You're such a spoiled brat.
You're a little fishy.
I'm just saying...
If the sensitive results turn out to be wrong...
I won't be satisfied.
What's that?
What's that? That's the funniest thing I've ever heard.
What's wrong with you?
I knew it. So help me out.
Right.Yeah.
Let's do our best.
The purpose of the project will change.
Suzuki Chigawa Kojima Alliance
Yes, let's go!
Let's make it happen.
It's not going to work, is that okay?
No, it's an alliance.
It's an alliance.
It's a deal.
We can form an alliance with anyone as long as we can negotiate.
There's bullying going on with Aoi Fuyashi... and it's been a while.
I haven't heard that in a while
Let's do our best in the third round.
I'll do my best.
I'd like to give Moeka a chance here.
It's an emergency plan.
Are you confident you can spot Moka?
I'll do my best!
I drink all the time.
Oh!
Oh! Delicious!
I'm with you, aren't I?
Yummy.
Surprisingly, the package is still the same.Surprisingly, the package is still the same.
I can't tell it's our laugh! No?
I want a drink.
Change of rules!
No! I'm confident enough to drink.
I want a drink.
No! No! No, no, no, no, no!
I want to drink.
Rule change.